Wen Jen

Web Developer

Wjen1214@qmail.com | https://qithub.com/wjen | linkedin.com/in/wen-jen | (626) 893-4331 | www.iamwenjen.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

My name is Wen and I am a Web Developer with experience in Javascript, React, and the MEAN stack. I am enthusiastic about new technology which has led me to become a web developer. My journey began by taking a few online programming courses and has since ignited my passion for the field which led me to General Assembly's Web Immersion Program. Ever since I have been driven to continuously learn and refine my skills. I now plan to apply my talents and passion to a Web Developer position.

SKILLS AND STRENGTHS

Primary language: JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS

Libraries & Frameworks: React, Angular, ¡Ouery, Node, Express, Flask, Django, Mongoose

Build Tools: Bootstrap, Materialize, Gulp, Sass, Webpack, Flexbox

Database: MongoDB, Postgresql, SQL

Other Related Skills: API, GraphQL, Agile Development, SCRUM, Github Workflow, Wireframing

Foreign Languages: Proficient in Mandarin

PROJECTS

REACT-CHATROOMS: A react messaging app that allows users to sign in with a username and specify a chatroom to chat live with others connected to the app. Socket.IO is used to provide real time messaging.

Technologies used: React | Socket.io | Javascript | Node

RESTAURANT REVIEWS: A progressive web app used to CRUD reviews from a node/sails.js api server. Utilizes service

workers, cacheDB and indexDB to provide an offline experience.

Technologies used: Service workers | Javascript | CSS | Gulp | IndexDB | CacheDB | API

CASEGALAXY: An E-commerce app that allows users to make purchases through Paypal from a list of items. The app

takes in Paypal API and allows users to CRUD listings with AJAX calls to the Mongo database. Technologies used: MEAN Stack | JSON Web Tokens | HTML | CSS | Gulp | Angular | Javascript

ECOMMERCE-DJ: An ebay like app built with Django and Python. Allows users to sign in and register with Django and

sallite. Users are able to comment, like, create and delete posts for listings.

Technologies used: Django | Python | SqlLite | Bootstrap

WORK EXPERIENCE

General Assembly · Los Angeles, CA

12-week web development program consisting of 3 months study both in-class and after hours. During the course I completed 4 projects including one group project, in one-week sprints.

Focal Electronics · El Monte, CA

June 2018 - June 2020

Owner

Online business with seller accounts in Ebay, Walmart, Amazon. Sold products sourced from China and locally.

Noir Collections · Diamond Bar, CA

June 2015 - Jan 2020

Manager

- Responsible for listing products on Amazon and Ebay while optimizing for listing algorithms.
- Implemented marketing strategies for higher rankings.

Citigroup Global Markets /JP Morgan Chase Bank · Arcadia, Ca

Oct 2011 - May 2015

Licensed Personal Banker

• Responsible for generating growth in customer relationships through sales, marketing, promotion and referral of products and services utilizing a proactive and disciplined approach.

EDUCATION